Guide to the Sam Kindrick Papers
The Wittliff Collections
- Action Magazine Issues, 1975-2018
  - 1996 Issues
    - Ric Marley cover, October, 1996 (Box 26)
    - Funfest cover, November, 1996 (Box 26)
    - December, 1996. Christmas cover (2), November, 1996 (Box 26)
  - 1997 Issues
    - Ruben V cover, January, 1997 (Box 26)
    - Townes Van Zandt cover (3), February, 1997 (Box 26)
    - Drugstore Cowboys cover, March, 1997 (Box 26)
    - Jimmy Spacek cover, April, 1997 (Box 26)
    - Tobacco cover (2), May, 1997 (Box 26)
    - Dino Lee cover, June, 1997 (Box 26)
    - Danny Barnes (Bad Livers) cover (2), July, 1997 (Box 26)
    - Mary Cutrufello cover, August, 1997 (Box 26)
    - Robbie G. cover, October, 1997 (Box 26)
    - Ray Wylie Hubbard cover (3), November, 1997 (Box 26)
    - Holiday package cover, December, 1997 (Box 26)
  - 1998 Issues
    - Jimmy Spacek, Paul Kandera cover, January, 1998 (Box 27)
    - Herb Carroll cover, February, 1998 (Box 27)
    - Creed Taylor cover, March, 1998 (Box 27)
    - Frankie Collins, April, 1998 (Box 27)
    - Claude Morgan cover, May, 1998 (Box 27)
    - Charlie Wood cover, June, 1998 (Box 27)
    - Meister & Daniels cover, July, 1998 (Box 27)
    - "South Paw" Paul Daffin (tattoo artist) cover, August, 1998 (Box 27)
    - "The Road Back Home" editorial cover (2), September, 1998 (Box 27)
    - Joe Horn cover, October, 1998 (Box 27)
    - Jody Jenkins cover, November, 1998 (Box 27)
    - Johnny Rodriguez trial cover (2), December, 1998 (Box 27)
  - 1999 Issues
    - Maya & Magaly cover, January, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Augie Meyers cover (3), February, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Boxing cover (2), March, 1999 (Box 27)
    - David & Lisa Huff cover, April, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Moon Moehring (blacksmith) cover, May, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Zone cover, June, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Kinky Friedman cover (2), July, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Tracy Conover cover, August, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Adam Carroll cover, September, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Russ & Randy Toman cover, October, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Ray Liberto cover, November, 1999 (Box 27)
    - Jim Spicer cover, December, 1999. (Box 27)
  - 2000 Issues
    - Eric Friedland, Los #3 Dinners cover, January, 2000 (Box 27)
    - Augie Meyers cover, February, 2000 (Box 27)
    - Frank Mueller (The Trap owner) cover, March, 2000 (Box 27)
    - Hank Williams III cover, April, 2000 (Box 27)
    - Sean Castillo cover (2), May, 2000 (Box 27)
    - Floyd Tillman cover (2), June, 2000 (Box 27)
    - Amanda Pearce cover, July, 2000 (Box 27)
    - Regina Matthews, Billy Mata cover, August, 2000 (Box 27)
    - Steve Silbas & Barbara Wolfe (Casbeers owners) cover, September, 2000 (Box 27)
    - Cave Catt Sammy cover (2), October, 2000 (Box 27)
    - Spot Barnett cover, November, 2000 (Box 27)
    - Brett Butler cover, December, 2000 (Box 27)
  - 2001 Issues
    - Robbie G cover, January, 2001 (Box 27)
    - D.A. Susan Reed cover, February, 2001 (Box 27)
    - Marc Benno cover, March, 2001 (Box 27)
    - James Snapp (tattoo artist), Jartse Tuominen cover (2), April, 2001 (Box 27)
    - Clay Blaker cover (2), May, 2001 (Box 27)
    - Geronimo Treviño cover, June, 2001 (Box 27)
    - Clifton Jansky cover, July, 2001 (Box 27)
    - Slim Roberts cover, August, 2001 (Box 27)
    - Brigitte London cover (2), September, 2001 (Box 27)
    - Sisters Morales cover, October, 2001 (Box 27)
    - Tony Ayala (boxer) cover, November, 2001 (Box 27)
    - Beth Williams cover, December, 2001 (Box 27)
  - 2002 Issues
    - Al Barlow cover, January, 2002 (Box 27)
    - Randy Garibay cover (2), February, 2002 (Box 27)
    - Stephanie Urbina Jones cover, March, 2002 (Box 27)
    - Roy Barnett (Deer Crossing Saloon owner) cover (2), April, 2002 (Box 27)
    - Mike Blakely, Maria Muldaur, Laurie Sky cover (2), May, 2002 (Box 27)
    - Randy Beltran Gariba "Chicano Bluesman" in memoriam cover (3), June, 2002 (Box 27)
    - Gary P. Nunn cover, July, 2002 (Box 27)
    - Thomas Michael Riley cover, August, 2002 (Box 27)
    - Bobby Rey cover, September, 2002 (Box 27)
    - Augie Meyers, Doug Sahm, other musicians cover, October, 2002 (Box 27)
    - Billy Joe Shaver, Kinky Friedman, Mason Ruffner cover, November, 2002 (Box 27)
    - Holiday issue cover, December, 2002 (Box 27)
  - 2003 Issues
    - Katherine Dawn, Rosie Ledet, Bob & Bear cover, January, 2003 (Box 27)
    - Sisters Morales cover, February, 2003 (Box 27)
    - Clifton Jansky cover, March, 2003 (Box 27)
    - Danni Leigh cover, April, 2003 (Box 27)
    - Jimmy Spacek cover, May, 2003 (Box 27)
    - John Goode (Action columnist) in memoriam cover, June, 2003 (Box 27)
    - Ruben V cover, July, 2003 (Box 27)
    - Ernie Garibay cover, August, 2003 (Box 27)
    - Smoking ban cover, September, 2003 (Box 27)
    - Bugs Henderson cover, October, 2003 (Box 27)
    - "Smush" cover, November, 2003 (Box 27)
    - Shelley King cover, December, 2003 (Box 27)
  - 2004 Issues
    - Miss Nessie (Ear Food) cover, January, 2004 (Box 28)
    - Century Music School of Guitar cover, February, 2004 (Box 28)
    - Albert Flores cover, March, 2004 (Box 28)
    - Graham Warwick cover, April, 2004 (Box 28)
    - Bettye Jean Moore cover, May, 2004 (Box 28)
    - Dale Watson cover (2), June, 2004 (Box 28)
    - Johnny Rod cover, July, 2004 (Box 28)
    - Susan Gibson cover, August, 2004 (Box 28)
    - Luke Olson cover, September, 2004 (Box 28)
    - Barefoot Larry's Tradition String Band cove, October, 2004 (Box 28)
    - Anthill Society cover, November, 2004 (Box 28)
    - Johnny Bush cover, December, 2004 (Box 28)
  - 2005 Issues
    - Clifton Jansky cover, January, 2005 (Box 28)
    - Herb Carroll (cowboy hatter), February, 2005 (Box 28)
    - Kinky Friedman for Governor cover, March, 2005 (Box 28)
    - 30 Year Anniversary cover (2), April, 2005 (Box 28)
    - Moe Bandy cover, May, 2005 (Box 28)
    - Stephanie Urbina Jones, Johnny Bush cover, June, 2005 (Box 28)
    - Pauline Reese cover (2), July, 2005 (Box 28)
    - Ram Ayala (Taco Land) in memoriam cover (2), August, 2005 (Box 28)
    - Steve Tombstone cover, September, 2005 (Box 28)
    - Shawn Sahm cover, October, 2005 (Box 28)
    - Darrell McCall cover (2), November, 2005 (Box 28)
    - McKay Brothers, Kate Mangold, Ron Knuth cover (2), December, 2005 (Box 28)
  - 2006 Issues
    - Rusty Martin cover, January, 2006 (Box 28)
    - Rick Broussard, Wayne Wilson cover, February, 2006 (Box 28)
    - Frank Mueller cover (2), March, 2006 (Box 28)
    - Mike Sanders cover, April, 2006 (Box 28)
    - Ruben V cover, May, 2006 (Box 28)
    - Adeline Cuesta cover, June, 2006 (Box 28)
    - Bobby Flores cover, July, 2006 (Box 28)
    - Kinky Friedman for Governor cover (3), August, 2006 (Box 28)
    - Houston Marchman cover (2), September, 2006 (Box 28)
    - Sean Castillo cover, October, 2006 (Box 28)
    - Will Own-Gage cover, November, 2006 (Box 28)
    - McKay Brothers, Bill Wirtz, Alex Habeeb cover, December, 2006 (Box 28)
  - 2007 Issues
    - Russell & Randy Tomans, Bobby Flores cover, January, 2007 (Box 28)
    - Shandon Sahm cover (2), February, 2007 (Box 28)
    - Richard Smith cover, March, 2007 (Box 28)
    - Johnny Bush cover (2), April, 2007 (Box 28)
    - KEXL FM cover, May, 2007 (Box 28)
    - Jimmy Spacek cover, June, 2007 (Box 28)
    - Petey the Wonder Dog cover (3), July, 2007 (Box 28)
    - Hector Saldaña (Krayolas) cover (3), August, 2007 (Box 28)
    - Claude Morgan cover, September, 2007 (Box 28)
    - Joe King Carrasco cover (2), October, 2007 (Box 28)
    - Carolyn Wonderland, Chris Holzhaus, Ken Raba cover, November, 2007 (Box 28)
    - Holiday cover, December, 2007 (Box 28)
  - 2008 Issues
    - Dale Watson cover, January, 2008 (Box 28)
    - Kinky Friedman & Steve Fromholz cover (2), February, 2008 (Box 28)
    - Benny Harp cover (2), March, 2008 (Box 28)
    - Clinton Baermann cover, April, 2008 (Box 28)
    - Vito Talerico cover, May, 2008 (Box 28)
    - Kirk Scott cover, June, 2008 (Box 28)
    - Darrell McCall cover (2), July, 2008 (Box 28)
    - Shelley King cover, August, 2008 (Box 28)
    - Ruthie Foster cover, September, 2008 (Box 28)
    - Wilbert Beasley cover, October, 2008 (Box 28)
    - James Hand cover, November, 2008 (Box 28)
    - Simmons Allison cover, December, 2008 (Box 28)
  - 2009 Issues
    - Kelly Spinks, Clay McClinton cover, January, 2009 (Box 29)
    - Max Baca and Los Texmaniacs cover, February, 2009 (Box 29)
    - Greg Coplen cover, March, 2009 (Box 29)
    - Mark Benno cover, April, 2009 (Box 29)
    - Bethany Owen cover, May, 2009 (Box 29)
    - Johnny Bush cover, June, 2009 (Box 29)
    - Kelly Hargraves, Elijah Zane cover, July, 2009 (Box 29)
    - Kevin Lewis & Dana Clark cover, August, 2009 (Box 29)
    - Rusty Martin Cover, September, 2009 (Box 29)
    - Stefania Baldesarelli (belly dancer) cover, October, 2009 (Box 29)
    - James Snap (tattoo artist) cover, November, 2009 (Box 29)
    - ReBeca cover, December, 2009 (Box 29)
  - 2010 Issues
    - Jeff Griffith cover (2), January, 2010 (Box 29)
    - Gurf Morlix cover (2), February, 2010 (Box 29)
    - Terri Sampley cover, March, 2010 (Box 29)
    - Steve James cover, April, 2010 (Box 29)
    - John Arthur Martinez cover (2), May, 2010 (Box 29)
    - Guy Forsyth cover, June, 2010 (Box 29)
    - Kenny Penny cover, July, 2010 (Box 29)
    - Geronimo Treviño cover, August, 2010 (Box 29)
    - Katherine Dawn (Texas Ladybugs) cover, September, 2010 (Box 29)
    - Mark Farner cover, October, 2010 (Box 29)
    - Maynard Brothers cover, December, 2010 (Box 29)
  - 2011 Issues
    - Wayne Harper, January, 2011 (Box 29)
    - Mike Ellis, February, 2011 (Box 29)
    - Jay Pennington (shelter dogs) cover, March, 2011 (Box 29)
    - Al Dean, Frank Pugliese cover, April, 2011 (Box 29)
    - Augie Meyers cover, May, 2011 (Box 29)
    - Suzy Bravo cover, June, 2011 (Box 29)
    - Patty Lou Reisz, Carlos Padilla (Olmos Pharmacy owners), July, 2011 (Box 29)
    - Karaoke cover, August, 2011 (Box 29)
    - Neka Scarbrough Jenkins cover, September, 2011 (Box 29)
    - Jerry King cover, October, 2011 (Box 29)
    - Claude Morgan cover (2), November, 2011 (Box 29)
    - San Antonio Rose Live Band cover, December, 2011 (Box 29)
  - 2012 Issues
    - Dub Robinson (Drugstore Cowboys) cover, January, 2012 (Box 29)
    - Emilio cover (2), February, 2012 (Box 29)
    - Johnny Cockerell cover, March, 2012 (Box 29)
    - Big John Oaks (Big john's Hangin' Tree Saloon) cover, April, 2012 (Box 29)
    - Ronnie Branham cover (2), May, 2012 (Box 29)
    - Mary Ann's Pig Stand cover, June, 2012 (Box 29)
    - Krayolas cover, July, 2012 (Box 29)
    - Karen Dittman cover, August, 2012 (Box 29)
    - Natalie Rose Capparelli cover, September, 2012 (Box 29)
    - Johnny Rodriguez, Texas Pride Barbecue cover, October, 2012 (Box 29)
    - Sylvia Kirk cover, November, 2012 (Box 29)
    - Elf Louise Locker cover, December, 2012 (Box 29)
  - 2013 Issues
    - Ron Young cover, January, 2013 (Box 29)
    - Ray Wylie Hubbard cover, February, 2013 (Box 29)
    - Alana Urbano cover, March, 2013 (Box 29)
    - Thurman Love (chef) cover, April, 2013 (Box 29)
    - Kevin Geil (Two Tons of Steel) cover, May, 2013 (Box 29)
    - Mitch Webb (The Swindles) cover, June, 2013 (Box 29)
    - Darrell McCall cover, July, 2013 (Box 29)
    - Wayne Harper's Martinis cover, August, 2013 (Box 29)
    - Granvil Poynter cover, September, 2013 (Box 29)
    - Bonnie Lang cover, October, 2013 (Box 29)
    - Steve Earle cover, November, 2013 (Box 29)
    - Rex Foster cover, December, 2013 (Box 29)
  - 2014 Issues
    - Pat Carroll cover (2), February, 2014 (Box 29)
    - Bruce Embrey cover (2), March, 2014 (Box 29)
    - Victoria Celestine (2), April, 2014 (Box 29)
    - Dale Watson cover (2), May, 2014 (Box 29)
    - Johnny Bush cover (2), June, 2014 (Box 29)
    - Curley Mays cover (3), July, 2014 (Box 29)
    - Mike Clancey cover (2), September, 2014 (Box 29)
    - Ron Knuth cover, October, 2014 (Box 29)
    - Amber Digby cover (2), November, 2014 (Box 29)
    - George Chambers (2), December, 2014 (Box 29)
  - 2015 Issues
    - Tex Pop (Museum) cover. Margaret Moser. (2), January, 2015 (Box 30)
    - Laurabell cover (2), February, 2015 (Box 30)
    - Royce Showalter cover (2), March, 2015 (Box 30)
    - 40th Anniversary Issue cover (2), April, 2015 (Box 30)
    - Kinky Friedman cover (2), May, 2015 (Box 30)
    - Jack Orbin cover (2), June, 2015 (Box 30)
    - Kathleen Sullivan cover (2), July, 2015 (Box 30)
    - Heyoka cover (2), August, 2015 (Box 30)
    - Sam and Lisa Asvestas cover (2), September, 2015 (Box 30)
    - Edgar Boeck cover (2), October, 2015 (Box 30)
    - Honest Charlie cover (2), November, 2015 (Box 30)
    - Chasca cover (2), December, 2015 (Box 30)
  - 2016 Issues
    - Amy Heller cover (2), January, 2016 (Box 30)
    - Jamie Balagia cover (2), February, 2016 (Box 30)
    - Ruben V / Jim Chestnut cover (2), March, 2016 (Box 30)
    - Blake Simpson cover (2), April, 2016 (Box 30)
    - Dale Watson & Chicken Shit Bingo cover (2), May, 2016 (Box 30)
    - Karen Barbee Adkisson cover (2), June, 2016 (Box 30)
    - Marty Haggard Cover (2), July, 2016 (Box 30)
    - George Chambers cover (2), August, 2016 (Box 30)
    - Russell and Randy Toman cover (2), September, 2016 (Box 30)
    - Augie Meyers cover (2), October, 2016 (Box 30)
    - Sam and Sharon Kindrick cover (2), November, 2016 (Box 30)
    - Alex Harvey cover (2), December, 2016 (Box 30)
  - 2017 Issues
    - Randy Toman, Jr. cover (2), January, 2017 (Box 30)
    - Mardi Gras cover, February, 2017 (Box 30)
    - Rex Foster cover (2), March, 2017 (Box 30)
    - Sauce Gonzalez and the Westside Horns cover, April, 2017 (Box 30)
    - Lyle Tuttle (tattoo artist) and Sam Kindrick cover, May, 2017 (Box 30)
    - Lacy Brinson cover, June, 2017 (Box 30)
    - Kay Maynard (Herb's Hats) cover, July, 2017 (Box 30)
    - Billy Mata cover, August, 2017 (Box 30)
    - Augie Meyers cover, September, 2017 (Box 30)
    - Ty Gavin cover, October, 2017 (Box 30)
    - 42nd anniversary cover, November, 2017 (Box 30)
    - Master Blaster (male stripper) cover, December, 2017 (Box 30)
  - 2018 Issues
    - Sam & Elsa Cedillo (Cowtown Boots) cover, January, 2018 (Box 30)
    - Hank Harrison cover, February, 2018 (Box 30)
    - Jerry Jeff Walker cover, March, 2018 (Box 30)
    - Frank Rodarte cover, April, 2018 (Box 30)
    - Greg Mastalerz cover, May, 2018 (Box 30)
    - Will Owen Gage cover, June, 2018 (Box 30)
    - Joey Villarreal (Blue Star Brewing), July, 2018 (Box 30)
- Artifacts
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the artifacts relating to Action Magazine.
  - Wire newspaper stand with Action Magazine logo